(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-06T00:47:38.426978",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: To all visitors]
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration now open!
演出の都合上 照明の明滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援 OK です
[Notice] Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance / Loud cheering is allowed
ローソンへお越しのみなさん
To everyone visiting Lawson,
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
[Lawson Campaign Announced!]
今回はこの6人が登場！
[Featuring these 6 members this time!]
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
[Details to be released on Monday, March 9!]
今年のバンダイブースも激熱！
This year's Bandai booth is super exciting too!
注目の新商品も初公開！
Featured new products unveiled for the first time!
会場限定！スペシャルフォトブース！
Venue exclusive! Special photo booth!
限定カードももらえる！
Get exclusive cards too!
期待プロジェクトも公開！来場してね！
Upcoming projects revealed! Come visit us!
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams 開演までしばらくお待ちください
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams - The concert will start soon
Attention ご来場のお客様へ：演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援 OK です
Attention for Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights / Loud cheering is OK
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. / Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams PENLIGHT COLORS
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams - PENLIGHT COLORS
hololive Dreams 事前登録受付中！
hololive Dreams - Pre-registration Open Now!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's all because you were there.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over again,
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now!
さあ乗り込もうっぞ！
Come on, let's jump aboard!
ridin' on dreams
Yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
Yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a tiny dream,
想像できないような
it turned into feelings
想いになったんだ
beyond imagination.
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we lose our way,
絆が船になる
our bond becomes our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
we can blow it right away!
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey,
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
there will be hardships along the way.
それも力に変えて
But we'll turn even those into strength
一緒に進むんだよ！
and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's all because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, this won't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves,
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining as myself.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you
ねえ、宝物だから
is my greatest treasure,
手を取り合い声かけ合って
so holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world without a map,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden gust of wind
行く先乱そうとも
tries to disrupt our path,
あの日誓ったんだ
we swore on that day,
覚悟は揺るがない
our determination will not waver!
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
Pushing ourselves to do our best
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to treasure this even more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship,
どっから始めているかもがいて
struggling, wondering where to even begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
forming a circle little by little, we found
何にも代えられない夢だ
an irreplaceable dream!
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Loving even what's unfinished,
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
our feelings are as one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
わずかな希望でも
Even if it's a slender hope,
僕と君でずっと
with you and me, forever,
馬鹿にされても
even if people make fun of us,
信じたい！
I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" is not enough,
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
hey, my feelings are overflowing,
ずっと一緒だよ！
we'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's all because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, this won't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves,
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining as myself.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you
ねえ、宝物だから
is my greatest treasure,
手を取り合い声かけ合って
so holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world without a map,
まだまだ行けるから！
we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Getting back up again and again,
笑い合っていたい
I want us to keep smiling together.
願いだって
Even our wishes,
みんなで、さあ！
all together, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands and going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep on going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
Yeah!!
フブミオは夫婦
Fubumio is a married couple
ねねち愛してる
Nene-chi, I love you
エリート巫女 さくらみこ
Elite Miko Sakura Miko
あじあじ
Aji-aji
ホロメンが好きだ！！
I love Hololive members!!
ホロリスも好きだ！！
I love Hololive fans too!!
フブちゃん痛車で来た！！ from 高知
Came in a Fubu-chan itasha!! from Kochi
Ridin' on Dreams
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉 届け
May the words layered in harmony reach you...
たどたどしく描いては ぎこちないと笑ってた
We drew clumsily and laughed at how awkward it was
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
Predicting the future, let's see the continuation of that day
手と手繋いで 風も着こなして 扉を叩いて
Holding hands, taking the wind in stride, knocking on the door
連れて行くよ どんなこともきっと 一緒なら叶えていける
I'll take you along, because together we can surely make anything come true
ラララ 鳴りやまない 希望のベル ほら
La la la... look, the bell of hope that never stops ringing
ラララ 聞こえてる 聞こえてる 歌
La la la... can you hear it? This singing song
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉 鮮やかな 日々の向こう
Words layered in harmony beyond those vivid days
ずっと君と 描くよストーリー
Together with you forever, we'll draw our story
絆に 結んだ夢が
The dreams bound by our bonds
空へ 駆けていく
Are soaring up into the sky
きらめきに乗せて
Carried on the sparkles
あなたへ 届け
May it reach you
メロディ どこまでも
The melody, reaching everywhere
何気ないことも 愛おしい ひとりじゃないよ
Even ordinary moments are precious, you are not alone
ぎゅっ 見たい景色 楽しいムーブ
The view I want to see, fun moves,
魔法の言葉
and magic words.
ふっと息ついて ふっと振り返って
Taking a quick breath, looking back for a second,
また君を知って その度に
learning more about you each time.
ちょっと勇気出して
Muster up a little courage
明日へ飛び込んでいけ
and dive straight into tomorrow!
ララララ
La la la la
降り積もる導標はまだ
The signposts piling up are still...
ララララ
La la la la
覚えてる歌
a song I still remember.
ハーモニー
Harmony
手を伸ばしたら
When I reach out my hand,
足跡に虹がかかる
a rainbow arches over our footprints.
きっと叶える 未知掴むステージ
We'll surely make it come true, on this stage grasping the unknown.
ハーモニー
Harmony
記した場所へ運ぶ
Carrying us to the place we marked,
約束を輝きに乗せて
carrying our promise upon the shine.
世界へ
To the world,
響け
resonate,
メロディー いつまでも
melody, forevermore.
君と踏み出したあの一歩 あの瞬間が
That step I took with you, that very moment...
宝物だって胸を張る今
I stand proud now, calling it a treasure.
歩いて話して一緒に笑顔で行くんだ
Walking, talking, going forward together with a smile,
色褪せないまま
without ever fading away.
混ざり合う僕らの声ほら
Look, our voices blending together...
聞こえてる
I can hear it,
歌
the song.
ハーモニー
Harmony
重ねた言葉
The words we layered,
鮮やかな日々の向こう
beyond those vivid days.
ずっと君と彩るストーリー
A story always painted together with you.
ハーモニー
Harmony
結んだ夢が空へ駆けていく
The dreams we bound rush into the sky.
きらめきに乗せてあなたへ
Riding upon sparkles, straight to you.
世界へ
To the world,
愛を
love...
メロディーどこまでも
melody, wherever it goes.
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
呼び合う声も合図に
With our calling voices as the signal!
パレ パレ パレ 探しにいく
Parade, parade, parade, we're off to search!
スタートは何度だって
We can start over as many times as we want.
独り言 綴った
I jotted down my inner thoughts,
ただ 始まりたくて走った
just wanting to begin, so I ran.
遠く 暗がりにともった
Lit far away in the dark,
それは 眩しすぎた名前
that was a name far too dazzling.
それは 鮮やかすぎる思い出
Those were memories far too vivid.
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get closer,
思いがけず結び合った ほら 今
and unexpectedly, we connected—look, right now!
迷いは本気になった
My hesitation turned into real passion.
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
悔しさと愛しさの 連れておいで
Bring along the frustration and the love!
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな命の灯り
The modest light of life,
終わりなき兆し 君を見つけたこと
an endless sign—finding you...
胸を張れるよ ここから これから
I can hold my head high, from here on out.
Our Bright Parade Parade
まだ 頼りない予感を 歌を 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
There's nothing to be ashamed of with this still unreliable hunch, or song.
誰も 解けないイマジナリー
An imaginary world no one can unravel,
いつか また会えるおまじない
a magic spell to meet again someday.
ゼロに始まったストーリー
A story that started from zero,
数え切れないことのほうが多い
there are more things than we can count.
数えるような想いじゃないさ
These feelings aren't meant to be counted.
ほら 今 僕らを一つと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call ourselves one!
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ 美しいんだよ
Sunny, sunny, sunny, it's so beautiful!
許し合える切ない夜はきらめく
The bittersweet nights where we forgive each other sparkle.
雨 晴れ 晴れ 瞬かない空
Rain, sunny, sunny, an unblinking sky,
満たしたい時間は
the time I want to fill...
君とあることさ
...is the time spent with you.
君とあることなんだ
It's all about being with you.
「ただいま」を聞けば
When I hear "I'm home,"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
I'll shout back, "Welcome home!"
当たり前じゃないから
Because none of this is taken for granted.
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ 輝くんだよ
Sunny, sunny, sunny, it shines so bright!
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ
Filling up the darkness—it's you, it's me!
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ 輝くんだよ
Sunny, sunny, sunny, it shines so bright!
悔しさも愛おしさも連れておいで
Bring along both the frustrations and endearments!
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光
A modest prayer becomes light.
終わりなき兆し 君と
An endless sign, with you...
飛び込んでいく
...diving into...
素敵な瞬間さ
...such a wonderful moment.
僕から
From me,
これから
from now on,
あわい未来 晴れ 晴れ
a gentle future, sunny and bright.
ホロライブ 5th Fes. STAGE3! たくさん楽しんでいくぞー！
Hololive 5th Fes. STAGE 3! Let me hear you have a ton of fun!
ちわー！ ホロライブ2期生、大空スバルでーす！
Hello~! I'm Oozora Subaru from Hololive 2nd Generation!
みんなー、会いたかったぞー！
Everyone, I missed you all so much!
フェス2日目、始まる、始まるー！
Fes Day 2 is starting, starting now!
通知させて 愛情が先に 走り出す僕らのランウェイを
Let affection go first, running down our runway.
感情とラッキーを盾に 進みます Are you ready?
With emotion and luck as our shield, we move forward. Are you ready?
転んだって泣いたって僕ら 慣れてるよ 受け売りは Perfect
Even if we fall or cry, we're used to it; second-hand knowledge is perfect.
笑ってくれてありがとう また僕は歌えるよ
Thank you for smiling for me, I can sing once again.
人生は不安ばっか 正直自信はないけど
Life is full of anxieties, and honestly I lack confidence, but...
君の隣だけは 譲る気はないのです
...the spot right beside you is the one thing I won't give up!
僕らが出会えた奇跡の世界 君の目にどう映るかな
The miraculous world where we met, I wonder how it looks in your eyes.
青くより澄みわたる 僕だけの空だといいな
Clearer and bluer than ever, I hope it's a sky just for me.
不確かな永遠より僕は 二人で過ごす今を歌いたいんだ
Rather than an uncertain eternity, I want to sing about the "now" we spend together.
この星の片隅 続く AIM-ME 遊園地
In a corner of this planet, continuing as an Aim-Me amusement park.
ナンセンスな現実が 心乱していた
Nonsensical reality was throwing my heart into turmoil.
ラッキーの天秤の 裏側にあるアンラッキー
On the other side of luck's scales lies unluckiness.
転んだって泣いたって僕ら 立ち上がる七転八倒さ
Even if we fall or cry, we stand back up through all the struggles.
笑ってくれてありがとう まだ僕は走れるよ
Thank you for smiling for me, I can still keep running!
人生の期待感は 正直膨らむばかりでさ
My expectations for life honestly just keep swelling up.
君の心の中 灯る陽だまりなのです
Inside your heart, it's a sunny spot lighting up.
僕らが暮らしてる奇跡の時代 君のこと照らすかな
The miraculous era in which we live, I wonder if it illuminates you.
星よりきらめいた 僕らしさ色になれたら
More sparkling than stars, if I could become my true color...
不確かな永遠より僕は 二人で過ごす今を楽しんでいたい
Rather than an uncertain eternity, I want to enjoy the "now" we spend together.
この星の片隅 続く AIM-ME 遊園地
In a corner of this planet, continuing as an Aim-Me amusement park.
すこやかなときも やめるときも きっと
In sickness and in health, I surely...
伝えたいよ このメロディ
...want to convey this melody.
僕らが出会えた奇跡の世界 君の目にどう映ったかな
How did this miraculous world where we met look in your eyes?
青い空に澄み渡る 僕だけのそんな歌がいいな
I wish for a song just for me that clears through the blue sky.
不確かな永遠より僕は 2人で過ごす今を歌いたいんだ
Rather than an uncertain eternity, I want to sing about the 'now' we spend together.
この星の片隅に続く
Continuing in a corner of this star...
アイ マイ ミー ユー ユー に ラブ ミー アイ ラブ ユー
I, my, me, you, you love me, I love you,
スーパーアイドル！
Super Idol!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
ステージ2、楽しんでいくぞー！
Let's have fun in Stage 2!
I'm way too cool for this
I do my thing, no rules for this
I get that bag, it's lucrative
You curious?
Look closer
It's so obvious
How I can make a scene
Jump with my energy
I'll make you scream it loud, loud, loud
Hit it
Serve it up
On a platter, leave no crumbs
Ate it up
That's just my ego
It's your attention
That I crave on the stage, I feel it
Pumping through my veins
Comin' at you right now
It's my, it's my, it's my, it's my ego, go, go
Living for your applause
I'll dance on either way
XOXO Ego
Fueling up my fantasy, I'm breaking through
It's just my ego, go, go, ooh
I'm doing what they thought I couldn't do
XOXO Ego
The rise and fall
Of a popstar
Yeah, I'm on an ego trip
No mirage, all real, it ain't no trick
I don't hold my tongue, I know I'm it
I'm your favorite's favorite, I'm that bitch
Tabloids say
I'm conceited and they're right
Ain't no shame
Either way they're gonna write
"She's so explicit"
But stay in my mentions, huh?
Got your attention
Baby, that's show business
It's my, it's my, it's my, it's my ego, go, go
Living for your applause
I'll dance on either way
XOXO Ego
Fueling up my fantasy, I'm breaking through
It's just my ego, go, go, ooh
I'm doing what they thought I couldn't do
XOXO Ego
Ego
They say I'm a show-off
XOXO Ego
Ego
Don't like it? Tough luck
XOXO Ego
みんな一緒に！ EGO!
Everyone together! EGO!
I can't hear you!
EGO!
ラスト行くよー！
Here comes the last one!
EGO!
That's just my ego
XOXO
画策せよ！
Plot and scheme!
今日のフェスも盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let me see you all get hyped for today's fest too!
現地のみんなも、ネットで見ているみんなも、たくさん楽しんでいってね！
Everyone here at the venue and everyone watching online, have lots of fun!
行くぞー！
Here we go!
スローモーション 真珠者 みたいな
Like a slow-motion pearl-diver,
カラフル セロハン までの 伸び代
with margin for growth up to colorful cellophane,
匂い立つ たった今を 含めて 愛好
loving even this fragrant 'right now',
揺れながら 暇を 持て余した夜
a night spent swaying with time to spare.
私 また 昨日と 同じ 形 して 固まってる
I'm freezing up again, taking the exact same shape as yesterday.
ねえ 寒くて 前に 進めないの それくらい 察してよ 悲しい
Hey, it's so cold I can't move forward; at least notice that much... how sad.
終わり方
This way of ending.
ばかり話し考えたがっている
Always wanting to talk and overthink things,
まあそれで笑う角もないと 愛らしいふりをして
acting sweet, as if there's no reason to smile,
壁にしみついた 君が息をした跡が この部屋に漂った
The traces of your breath stained on the walls lingered in this room,
酸素を腐らせて 私を死にたらしめる
rotting the oxygen and leading me to my death.
テラモ... 浸透 闇体が 快楽線まで伸びる
Teramote... penetrating, the dark body extends to the line of pleasure,
匂いを抱いた 幸福 メデタイガール
A happy, naive girl cradling the scent,
揺れながら 暇を持て余している
swaying around, killing time.
しかし また昨日と同じ 轍 抜けなくなっている
Yet stuck in the same rut as yesterday, unable to break free,
ねえ だるくて体動かないの 今日くらい 優しくして
Hey, I'm feeling sluggish and can't move—be gentle with me today at least.
寂しい 言葉を垂れ流し 晒し 跨がり合っている
Spouting lonely words, exposing them, straddling each other,
もう それで済むなら言うこともないと 諦視して 夢を覚まさせて
If that settles it, I've got nothing to say; resignation set in, wake me from this dream.
君が好きな ヒーローのようには
Unlike the hero you love,
いつか 消えてしまわないように
so that I don't vanish into thin air someday,
手口を明かしたら 終わらない夜が訪れる
reveal the trick, and an endless night will arrive.
テラモ... 真実 見えないが
Teramote... can't see the truth, but
桃源郷 行きと明かしまして
declaring we're headed for Shangri-La,
総力戦 語りたいが
I want to talk about total warfare,
今はただ 薫りを浮べ
but for now, I just let the fragrance float.
イェーイ！みんな手拍子して！
Yay! Everyone, clap your hands!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
長い 長い 闇を彷徨って 笑い方も 忘れてしまった
Wandering through the long, long darkness, I forgot how to laugh.
悲劇のストーリーが 私の心 狂わせる
A tragic story drives my heart crazy.
テラモ... 浸透 闇体が 快楽線まで伸びる
Teramote... penetrating, the dark body extends to the line of pleasure,
匂いを抱いた 幸福 メデタイガール 揺れながら 暇を持て余してる
A happy, naive girl cradling the scent, swaying around, killing time.
どうせ 真実 見えないが
Can't see the truth anyway, but
桃源郷 行きと明かしまして
declaring we're headed for Shangri-La,
総力戦 語りたいが
I want to talk about total warfare,
今はただ 薫りを浮べ
but for now, I just let the fragrance float.
噛んじゃった！
I stumbled!
また噛んだ...
Stumbled again...
まだまだ行くぞー！
We're not done yet, let's go!
エリザベス・ローズ・ブラッドフレイム
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
ジジ・ムリン
Gigi Murin
セシリア・イマーグリーン
Cecilia Immergreen
ラオーラ・パンテーラ
Raora Panthera
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below, takin' you all below
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, below we go
They think they want it
They wanna get, get down
We take 'em down, down, down
Queendom in the borderline
Run it, no surprise
You ain't gonna win, but you can try
Told ya, you got no luck, end up in my lineup
Listen, listen
Run or hide and scream out, already locked ya up
Fool's games you always play
Call me corrupt, won't hear anything
Aiming my sight down right on your heart
Throwin' the keys out, shut down
JUSTICE! Like that! JUSTICE! Get that!
You're never forgiven, no one to just forget
Higher, higher, higher...
You're standing on the edge...
Edge, don't know me, I'm unpredictable, typical you
Got nowhere to go, show you something real, my level
Though you'll never know, as above, so...
みんな！盛り上がってるー？
Is everyone hyped up?!
Run in the light, oh my dear, what's wrong, what's right
Dancing in a fantasy, wanna be diseased, show that you will never make it out
Eyes fall now, and do it, do it, need to get a license for it now, now, enemies go lock down, oh!
See your guilty heart, we're not gonna stop, it's just...
...START!
Get down, get down, let's go, let's go
Bring up the flow below, which you already know, don't shy, bingo, it's...
Run in the light, oh my dear, what's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night, oh my dear, come be caught
Another ending in the dark, love is something just like THAT! JUSTICE! THAT!
We rise!
Standing on the edge, don't know me, I'm unpredictable, typical you, got nowhere to go
Show you something real, my level, though you'll never know, as above, so...
...and below, you should know
Just a little unpredictable, typical, just look at, look at, baby
Go now, and goes below!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ハロー！
Hello!
まず、じゃあ自己紹介しようか！
First, shall we introduce ourselves?
そうだね！うん！
That's right! Yeah!
みんなー！あん肝ー！
Everyone! Ankimo!
元気ー？ときのそらでーす！
How are you doing? I'm Tokino Sora!
ハーイ！カバー株式会社 ホロライブプロダクション所属
Hi! Belonging to Cover Corporation's Hololive Production,
オレンジ色担当 5期生、ねぽらぼのねん！
in charge of orange, 5th Gen, NePoLaBo's Nene!
みんなの心の...？
In everyone's heart...?
最高だー！桃鈴ねねでーす！よろしくー！
You guys are the best! I'm Momosuzu Nene! Nice to meet you!
おー、すごいねー！
Wow, that's awesome!
ていうか、ねねとぬんのペア珍しくない？
By the way, isn't this pairing of Nene and Nun-nun pretty rare?
本当だ！珍しいよねー！
You're right! It really is rare!
最前線にねっ子いるじゃん！ねっ子いるじゃん！
Look, there are Nekko right in the front row! Nekko are here!
イエーイ！あ、そらとも様も見えてるよー！
Yay! Ah, I can see Soratomo-sama too!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
今日は何？なんと、なんと2日目！
What is today? It's actually Day 2!
そうだね！昨日からだから2日目だー！
That's right! Since it started yesterday, today is Day 2!
え、昨日から連日来てるよーって人ー！
Who here has been coming every day since yesterday?
おー！めっちゃいる！かなりいる！すごい！
Woah! There are so many! So many people! Amazing!
いつも来てくれてありがとうございます、本当に！
Thank you so much for coming as always, really!
今日初めて来た人ー！
Who came for the first time today?
いっぱいいるー！本当にみんな嘘ついてない？
There are so many! Are you guys sure you're not lying?
昨日から来てる気分の人もいるかもしれない！
Maybe some people just feel like they've been here since yesterday!
そうだよね！気分大事、大事！
Right! The mood is what matters most!
というわけでね、今回のフェスのテーマは「Capture the Moment」ということでね
So, the theme for this fes is "Capture the Moment," right?
みんなと架け橋の形があったじゃん？
We had that bridge-like setup to connect with everyone, right?
トロッコっていうやつが！トロッコ素晴らしかったね！
The moving carts! The moving carts were amazing!
みんなの近くに行ったよー！見えたかなー？
We went really close to everyone! Could you see us?
見えたかなー？
Could you see us?
えー、じゃあ今日のハッシュタグについてちょっとおさらいしていきたいと思います！
Well then, let's review today's hashtag!
フェス、EXPO...
Fest, EXPO...
2024 DAY2です！
2024, Day 2!
皆さん、たくさんポストしてください！
Everyone, please post a lot!
してください！
Please do!
確かに！
True!
じゃあ、何々？ちょっと聞いてみようかな。
Well then, what what? Let me ask!
おっ、何聞くの？
Oh, what are you going to ask?
日本の皆んなー！
Everyone from Japan!
海外アニキー！
Overseas bros!
おー、すごい！
Oh, wow!
すごいねー！
That's amazing!
いろんなところから来てくれてるよ！
People came from all over!
いやー、ありがとう！
Wow, thank you!
嬉しいね！
So happy!
違う違う違う！皆と喋る時間だから！
No no no! This is our time to talk with everyone!
こんなにたくさんの人の前でスケベができることなんて、なかなかないから...
Getting to be perverted in front of this many people doesn't happen often, so...
そういう意味だったの？！
That's what you meant?!
全然気づかなかった！
I didn't notice at all!
タッチさせてよ！
Let me touch you!
触っていい？
Can I touch?
あー！
Ah!
ぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽ...
Popopopopopopopo...
最高な気分だ、みんなー！
I feel amazing, everyone!
みんなも楽しんでるかー？！
Are you all enjoying yourselves too?!
せっかくさ、私たちがさ...
Since we...
うん。
Yeah.
MC一番手じゃん？
Are the very first MC slot, right?
うん、ねー！最初のMC任されちゃった！
Yeah, right! We were given the first MC!
そうだよ！だから、もう皆がやりそうなこと全部やっちゃおう！
Exactly! So let's do everything everyone else might do!
コーレスとか、ウェーブとか！
Like call-and-response, or waves!
コーレスで、ぬんにぴったりのやつ考えたから！
For call-and-response, I thought of something perfect for Nun!
何かある？
Got something?
「ぬんは今日もー」って聞いたら、みんなが「ぬんぬん」って返す！
If I ask "Is Nun today too—", everyone replies "Nun nun"!
普通にね、私がやりそうな気がした、それ。
Honestly, I felt like that's something I'd actually do.
ちょっとやってみよう、やってみよう！
Let's try it, let's try it!
もう一回言って。
Say it again.
「ぬんは今日もー」「ぬんは今日もー」、で、「ぬんぬん」？
"Is Nun today too—", "Is Nun today too—", then "Nun nun"?
あ、オッケー、オッケー、オッケー！
Ah, okay, okay, okay!
行くよー！
Here I go!
ぬんは今日もー！
Is Nun today too—!
にょにょー！
Nyo nyo~!
あっ、すごい！ペンライトもみんな青色で統一してくれてる！
Oh wow! Everyone unified their penlights in blue!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
え、ねねちは？ねねちはどうしよう？
Wait, what about Nenechi? What should Nenechi do?
ねねは今日もー... ねねは今日もー...
Nene is today too—... Nene is today too—...
何だろう？
What should it be?
え、これどこまでふざけていいんだろう？
Wait, how silly can I be with this?
え、いいんじゃない？100%ふざけよう、100%ふざけよう！
Isn't it fine? Go 100% silly, 100% silly!
じゃあ「ねねは今日もー」って言ったら...
Then if I say "Is Nene today too—"...
うん。
Yeah.
何言ってほしいの？
What do you want them to say?
「うんぴっぴ」とかあり？
Is "Unpippi" okay?
それ自分的にありなの？！
Is that okay for you personally?!
ありあり！イチオシなんだ！
Totally fine! It's my top recommendation!
じゃあ、海外アニキ、everybody say "うんぴっぴ", Let's go! 行くよー！
Then overseas bros, everybody say "Unpippi"! Let's go! Here we go!
ねねは今日もー！
Is Nene today too—!
言ってくれたー！
They said it!
最高、みんな！最高だよー！
You guys are the best! The best!
ねね、こんなにたくさんの人の前でこれ言うの恥ずかしい...！
Nene feels so embarrassed saying this in front of so many people...!
何言ってんの、めちゃくちゃ嬉しそうだったじゃん今！「やったー！」みたいな！
What are you talking about? You looked super happy just now! Like "Yay!"!
え、あれもやろう！あれ！
Oh, let's do that too! That!
何？
What?
ウェーブ！
The wave!
こっちから順番に... スタンバイ！スタンバイ、みんな！
From this side, in order... Standby! Standby, everyone!
ウェーブ... やりましょう！
Let's do the wave!
ウェーブやるよー！行くよー！
Doing the wave! Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set, go!
戻ろ！戻ろう！
Send it back! Send it back!
早い早い早い！
Fast, fast, fast!
戻って！戻ってー！
Send it back! Send it back!
まだついてきてない、みんなが！
Everyone hasn't caught up yet!
戻って戻ってー！
Send it back, send it back!
完璧だ、みんなー！
Perfect, everyone!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
みんな、でもここでね、あのお知らせしなきゃいけないことがある。
Everyone, but here, we have an announcement to make.
そうなんだよね、実はあるんだよね。
That's right, actually we do.
「えー」ってもう言われてる！何も言ってないのに「えー」って言われた！
They're already saying "Ehhh!"! We haven't said anything yet and they said "Ehhh!"!
みんな勘がいいね！勘がいいね！
Everyone is so sharp! So quick-witted!
じゃあ、ぬん、ちょっと大事なお知らせ...
Then, Nun, please make the important announcement...
あ、私なんだ！いいよー、って。
Ah, it's me! Sure thing!
YouTube、TikTokでご覧の方は、ここまでになってしまいます！
For those watching on YouTube or TikTok, this is where it ends!
なんてこったー！
Oh no~!
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは...
Everyone who still wants to hype up together...
概要欄から...
From the description section...
どこにあるか分からないけど、概要欄からぜひ...
I don't know where it is, but from the description section...
配信チケットに...
Please get a stream ticket...
来てねー！
And come join us!
というわけで、チラ見せはここまで！
So with that, the free sneak peek ends here!
せーの、ライブ アンド ドリーム！
Ready, set... Live & Dream!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.